

Edicleo Oliveira

Full Stack Developer

SOLID Design Patterns

BARUERI. SP START IMMEDIATELY REMOTE WORK IS A GREAT IDEA

Specialist. Focused on development for over 17 years. Controls hardware with low-level technologies, surprises with elegant highend desktop, web and mobile solutions. Quick reasoning, identifies and solves problems in a sustainable way. Always focused on quality, it guarantees easy maintenance and evolution of complex long-term solutions.













EXPERTISE

MAIN

EXPERIENCE TIME (IN YEARS)

1-3

4-6

7-10

11+

Desktop More than 17 years

Mobile More than 8 years

Web More than 13 years

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE



2022 **Senior Developer Analyst**

Sofashion Consultoria

MAR 2015 - DEC 2022

- Team leader in the development and implementation of e-commerce (web).
- API development for communication between web and mobile system.
- Contributed in the development of e-commerce application (Android).
- Consultant at information security area.

https://edicleo.dev 1/7 Amazon Web Services Bash C# CSS3 Azure DevOps C++ HTML 5 Django Docker DynamoDB ES6 Git Java Jetpack Compose Kotlin Kubernets Laravel Magento Maven MongoDB MVC MySQL NodeJS NoSQL PHP Python React.JS Redux Scrum SASS Redis Restful SOA SOL SQLite SQL Server

2014 **=** Full Developer Analyst

Stefanini Consultoria e Assessoria em Informática

FEB 2013 - DEC 2014

- Allocated in the Medical Area sector at Unimed-Rio, I was responsible for developing and maintaining essential systems for medical care, a web solution with more than 20,000 daily accesses.
- Responsible for major changes in the sector, such as restructuring and important implementations in the main system.
- Adjustment of the system to the standards imposed by the National Health Agency, such as communication between Unimed x ANS.
- Development of a solution responsible for communication between Unimed's in other states of the country, a service that processes more than 100 thousand daily requests.

Angular ASP ASP.NET C C++ C# CSS3 JavaScript jQuery

MVC .NET Framework Oracle DB PL/SQL Restful Scrum SASS

SOA SQL Team Foundation Server Windows Forms

2011 **Programmer**

Ambidados Consultoria em Meio Ambiente OCT 2013 - DEC 2011

- Founder, leader and main developer of an important tool for the Meteorology and Oceanography sector at Petrobras, capable of reducing response time by up to 30% in the processing and analysis of large data shipments.

 Development system to run as a service, processes highly complex mathematical calculations and performs an average of 15 million SQL statements per day.
- Migration of high complexity mathematical calculation technologies.
- Gave lectures on software development for scientists, data analysts and other programmers.

ASP ASP.NET Backend C Cobol C++ C# Frontend Java JavaScript MATLAB MVC .NET Framework Oracle DB PL/SQL Python Visual Basic VB.NET VB.NET WCF Windows Forms

PROJECTS

https://edicleo.dev

WE

FEB 2023 - TILL NOW

https://github.com/edicleoline/proxy

Hardware and software development for a 4G proxy server.

The equipment consists of a modified microcomputer and some manageable electronic components.

Talking about software, a solution that provides a Restful API and a web app to control the hardware, such as routing IPs, filters, IPv4 and IPv6 proxy, Socks4 and Socks5, routes, plugins for different models of modems and cell phones, user control, bandwidth control, SMS management, and others.

Bash CSS3 Debian Flask Full-Stack HTML 5 JavaScript Material UI NodeJS Python React.JS SASS Socketio SQL SQLite TypeScript Web

Truecall

NOV 2022 - TILL NOW

https://github.com/edicleoline/berners-truecaller

Identifier and blocker of unwanted calls and messages for cell phones.

Amazon Web Services Bash Full-Stack Java Jetpack Compose Kotlin Laravel Mobile MySQL NodeJS PHP Python Selenium SQL SQLite TDD **TypeScript**

EDUCATION



UERJ

Universidade Estadual do Rio de Janeiro Computer Science 2012 - 2016

TRAININGS





2018 Advanced Penetration Testing

HackerSec

OCT 2017 - JUL 2018

Intrusion Techniques in Corporate Networks.

2006 **Database**

FAETEC

JAN 2006 - OCT 2006

https://edicleo.dev 3/7 SQL, database administration, network administration and security, database analysis and modeling, Data Wharehousing and Data Mining.

2005 {} Java, OOP

FAETEC

MAR 2005 - NOV 2005

Java and Object Orientation, UML, JDBC, JavaFX, JPA, Hibernate.

2004 <> Programming

FAETEC

FEB 2004 - DEC 2004

Programming logic, Java, C#, C, C++, Javascript, Visual Basic, Games, Computing.

SKILLS

Django

Docker

More than 2 years

More than 2 years

MAIN EXPERIENCE TIME (IN YEARS)

0-1 2-3 4-6 7+

Angular More than 5 years ASP More than 11 years ASP.NET More than 8 years Amazon Web Services More than 8 years More than 10 years Bash Bootstrap Framework More than 5 years More than 13 years CI/CD More than 5 years Cobol More than 2 years C++ More than 12 years C# More than 12 years CSS3 More than 9 years Debian More than 10 years Delphi More than 2 years Azure DevOps More than 4 years

https://edicleo.dev 4/7

DynamoDB More than 4 years
ES6 More than 10 years
ESLint More than 7 years
Express.js More than 4 years
Figma More than 3 years
Flask More than 6 years
Flutter More than 2 years
Git More than 6 years
GraphQL More than 5 years
HTML 5 More than 9 years
Ionic Framework More than 5 years
Java More than 9 years
JavaScript More than 13 years
Jetpack Compose More than 5 years
jQuery More than 10 years
Kotlin More than 5 years
Kubernets More than 2 years
Laravel More than 5 years
MATLAB More than 1 year
Maven More than 4 years
Mocha More than 2 years
MongoDB More than 5 years
Material UI More than 4 years
MVC More than 8 years
.NET Framework More than 13 years
.NET Core More than 5 years
Next.js More than 4 years
NodeJS More than 6 years
NoSQL More than 5 years

https://edicleo.dev

Oracle DB More than 5 years
PHP More than 10 years
PL/SQL More than 2 years
PostgreSQL More than 6 years
Python More than 10 years
R More than 2 years
React.JS More than 6 years
Redis More than 5 years
Redux More than 6 years
Restful More than 9 years
Scrum More than 8 years
SASS More than 12 years
Selenium More than 5 years
Serverless More than 6 years
SOA More than 9 years
Socketio More than 5 years
SOLID More than 8 years
Spring Boot More than 4 years
Spring MVC More than 2 years
SQL More than 14 years
SQLite More than 8 years
SQL Server More than 6 years
TDD More than 10 years
TypeScript More than 5 years
Visual Basic More than 6 years
VB.NET More than 4 years
Vue.JS More than 2 years
WCF More than 5 years
WebSocket More than 8 years
Windows Forms More than 8 years

https://edicleo.dev 6/7

Yes, this project is on Github! https://github.com/edicleoline/resume

https://edicleo.dev 7/7